The East St. Louis Race Riot of 1917 on Microfilm 5749 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Witnesses on Behalf of the Defendant, 1919
  - N.W. Pardon., 1919; 17 (Reel 8)
    36pp.
  - James A. Gladden., 1919; 18 (Reel 8)
    13pp.
  - Arnold Ernest., 1919; 19 (Reel 8)
  - Dr. Thomas G. Hunter., 1919; 20 (Reel 8)
    15pp.
  - William W. Buchanan., 1919; 21 (Reel 8)
    11pp.
  - W.H. Mills., 1919; 22 (Reel 8)
- Series Witnesses for the Defendant, 1919
  March 26, 1919
  - O.A. Krebs., 1919; 23 (Reel 8)
    6pp.
  - J.C. Hennington., 1919; 24 (Reel 8)
    12pp.
  - Cora May Westbrook., 1919; 25 (Reel 8)
    9pp.
  - Daisy Westbrook., 1919; 26 (Reel 8)
  - Cora May Westbrook, Testimony cont., 1919; 27 (Reel 8)
    1p.
  - Daisy Westbrook, Testimony cont., 1919; 28 (Reel 8)
    2pp.
  - Henry Bayles., 1919; 29 (Reel 8)
    4pp.
  - Ben Colby., 1919; 30 (Reel 8)
  - George Weber., 1919; 31 (Reel 8)
  - Russell E. Townsend., 1919; 32 (Reel 8)
    3pp.
  - George T. Kyle., 1919; 33 (Reel 8)
  - Thomas William Gaither., 1919; 34 (Reel 8)
    16pp.
  - Anna Scott., 1919; 35 (Reel 8)
  - Allen Akins., 1919; 36 (Reel 8)
  - Belle Akins., 1919; 37 (Reel 8)
  - Julius May., 1919; 38 (Reel 8)
  - J.A. Lamply., 1919; 39 (Reel 8)
  - Mat Hayes, Testimony cont., 1919; 40 (Reel 8)
  - Ben Colby, Testimony cont., 1919; 41 (Reel 8)
  - Ida Bonham., 1919; 42 (Reel 8)
  - Mrs. William Kinney., 1919; 43 (Reel 8)
  - Anna McDaniels., 1919; 44 (Reel 8)
  - B.H. Ham., 1919; 45 (Reel 8)
  - William Mulconery., 1919; 46 (Reel 8)
  - Jay Long., 1919; 47 (Reel 8)
  - Oscar Wallace., 1919; 48 (Reel 8)
  - Dr. Earl Williams., 1919; 49 (Reel 8)
  - L.G. Cosley., 1919; 50 (Reel 8)
  - Julius Seifart., 1919; 51 (Reel 8)
  - Thomas Carten., 1919; 52 (Reel 8)
  - Calvin Cotner., 1919; 53 (Reel 8)
  - Arthur L. Conway., 1919; 54 (Reel 8)
  - Charles Eustache., 1919; 55 (Reel 8)
    8pp.
  - Calvin Cotner, Testimony cont., 1919; 56 (Reel 8)
  - Oliver Charles White., 1919; 57 (Reel 8)
  - Frank Davidson., 1919; 58 (Reel 8)
  - Georgia Smotherman., 1919; 59 (Reel 8)
  - Martha Johnson., 1919; 60 (Reel 8)
  - John Wright., 1919; 61 (Reel 8)
  - J.W. Hughes., 1919; 62 (Reel 8)
  - Dr. Lyman B. Blewett [Bluitt]., 1919; 63 (Reel 8)
  - Pearl Abernathy., 1919; 64 (Reel 8)
  - Charles Bundy., 1919; 65 (Reel 8)
  - Captain Robert A. Bird., 1919; 66 (Reel 8)
  - Benjamin H. Lucas., 1919; 67 (Reel 8)
  - William Red, Testimony cont., 1919; 68 (Reel 8)
  - Dr. LeRoy Bundy., 1919; 69 (Reel 8)
    94pp.
  - Albert R. Gardner., 1919; 70 (Reel 8)
- Series Witnesses for the Defendant, 1919
  March 27, 1919.
  - Albert R. Gardner, testimony cont., 1919; 71 (Reel 8)
  - Martha Campbell., 1919; 72 (Reel 8)
  - Laura Campbell., 1919; 73 (Reel 8)
  - Joe Campbell., 1919; 74 (Reel 8)
  - Elizabeth Stone., 1919; 75 (Reel 8)
- Series Last day of the trial, 1919
  March 28, 1919.
  - Instruction Given to the Jury on the Verdict., 1919; 76 (Reel 8)
  - Jury's Verdict., 1919; 77 (Reel 8)
  - Motion for New Trial., 1919; 78 (Reel 8)
  - Motion for Disqualification of Juror Daniel Davis, on Ground of Insanity., 1919; 79 (Reel 8)
  - Affidavits by Juror Stating Daniel Davis Was of Sound Mind., 1919; 80 (Reel 8)
  - Motion for Appeal., 1919; 81 (Reel 8)
  - Motion for Change of Venue., 1919; 82 (Reel 8)
  - Indictment Assignment of Errors., 1919; 83 (Reel 8)
  - Ordor for Bail., 1919; 84 (Reel 8)